开始了
I was so high
我是如此疯狂
I did not recognize
以至于没有察觉
The fire burning in her eyes
她眼里燃烧的火焰
The chaos that controlled my mind
混乱占据了我的思维
Whispered goodbye and she got on a plane
她轻声道别然后踏上飞机
Never to return again
从此一去不返
But always in my heart
但她永远在我心里
This love has taken its toll on me
这份爱让我付出了惨痛代价
She said Goodbye too many times before
她已经说过太多次再见
And her heart is breaking in front of me
她的心在我面前碎了一地
I have no choice cause I won't say goodbye anymore Come on
我别无选择，因为我不想再次道别   一起唱
I tried my best to feed her appetite
我曾经努力的取悦她
Keep her coming every night
每晚让她高潮迭起
So hard to keep her satisfied
用尽全力让她感到满足
Kept playing love like it was just a game
她却把爱情当成游戏
Pretending to feel the same
这次又假装没有感觉
Then turn around and leave again
然后转身再度离去
This love has taken its toll on me
这份爱让我付出了惨痛代价
She said Goodbye too many times before
她已经说过太多次再见
And her heart is breaking in front of me
她的心在我面前碎了一地
I have no choice cause I won't say goodbye anymore
我别无选择，因为我不想再次道别
举起手来
I'll fix these broken things
我要弥补这所有的错
Repair your broken wings
修复你的折翼
And make sure everything's alright
让一切都好起来
Its all right.Its all right
没事的 会好的
My pressure on your hips
我在你臀上的压力
Sinking my fingertips
渗透我的指尖
Into every inch of you
进入你的每一寸肌肤
Cause I know that's what you want me to do
因为我知道你要我这样做
This love has taken its toll on me
这份爱让我付出了惨痛代价
She said Goodbye too many times before
她已经说过太多次再见
And her heart is breaking in front of me
她的心在我面前碎了一地
I have no choice cause I won't say goodbye anymore
我别无选择，因为我不想再次道别
This love has taken its toll on me
这份爱让我付出了惨痛代价
She said Goodbye too many times before
她已经说过太多次再见
And her heart is breaking in front of me
她的心在我面前碎了一地
She said Goodbye too many times before
她已经说过太多次再见
让我听到你的呐喊声 里也人民！
我要听到更多人的声音 再次呐喊吧
我滴天 谢谢你们 里也的观众
只是多么多么不可思议的经历啊！ 我们是魔力红 谢谢你们
晚安！
耶  把手举起来！